{
    "id": "0cc4956925884f81b0de5ec87ef1bad2",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You don’t work on Sundays, .....................?",
            "description": "We use affirmative question tags after negative verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "don't you",
                "do you",
                "will you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They haven’t forgotten us, ..................... .?",
            "description": "We use affirmative question tags after negative verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "haven't they",
                "have they"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little point in doing anything about it, .......................?",
            "description": "Words like hardly and little are negative, so we use an affirmative tag after them.",
            "answers": [
                "is there",
                "isn't there",
                "was there"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t recognize him, .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "did she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You passed the test, ..................... ..?",
            "description": "When the sentence is in the simple past tense, we make question tags with did or didn't. ",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "did you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "They bought a new car last week, .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they",
                "hadn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She wants to be a writer, .......................?",
            "description": "When the sentence is in the simple present tense, we make question tags with do or does. ",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "has she",
                "hasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They make a lot of money, …..................... ..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "don't they",
                "have they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No one helped him, .......................?",
            "description": "Words like no and none are negative, so we use an affirmative tag after them. ",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "did they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She knows the answer, ............................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "has she",
                "don't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}